Asia Dhaher

UI/UX designer / Front-End / Biology

Masif-Erbil

+964 (783) 114 3663

asia.zahir2000@gmail.com

Profile

I am a UX/UI designer and front-end developer with a degree in biology and four years of experience in modern biology techniques. I am creative and innovative, and I always use design to solve user problems. I have a lot of experience in user workflows and UI/UX design. I use Figma to create wireframes, mockups, and prototypes. I love turning my designs into interactive web pages with Next.js and other developer tools.

Education

Bachelor's Degree, Salahaddin University - College of Science - Biology department, Erbil

AUGUST 2018 — JUNE 2021

Courses

English language course: Elementary, Cambridge College of English

JUNE 2019 — AUGUST 2019

The Web Developer Bootcamp 2021, By Colt Steele (Udemy)

AUGUST 2021 — JULY 2022

Intermediate - Advanced English, Lagus Online (Udemy)

JULY 2020 — SEPTEMBER 2020

Presentations: Speaking so that people listen, University of California (Coursera)

FEBRUARY 2021 — APRIL 2021

UI/UX Designer Bootcamp 2021, By Rwanga Foundation

OCTOBER 2021— DECEMBER 2021

Skills



Employment History

Biologist, Volunteer, Pirmam Health Center, Pirmam

APRIL 2021 — JUNE 2021

Front-End developer & UI/UX Designer, Full Time, Ovanya Company, Erbil

AUGUST 2022 — PRESENT

Projects

- 1. Design and develop two versions of my portfolio website.
- 2. Design and develop two private dashboards to Rudaw and KII.
- 3. Design and develop Ovanya website and Prime minister Masrour Barzani portfolio website.
- 4. Develop Grei agency website.
- 4. Web design for:
- · Sky marketing DOOH booking system private dashboard,
- · Government Traffic violation private dashboard,
- · YBS portfolio website,
- · K24 & Kurdistan Chronicle news website,
- EIF website,
- 5. Design and develop 3 WordPress websites. available one (kpacusa.org).
- 6. Design and create 2 Augmented Reality(AR) business cards. just for test and, I will develop my AR skill more.

Accounts

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/asia-zahir **Github** github.com/Asia-Dhahr

Behance behance.net/AsiaDh Portfolio asiia.vercel.app

Instagram Asia